

## **About Me**

I am a **software developer** with three years of experience. I've built multiple full-stack mobile & web applications. I have collaborated with clients to enhance and build software applications. I am seeking a role as **React Developer** to continue my passion for building things.

### Education

### **University of Montana**

Management Information Systems Aug 2013 - Jan 2018

## **Skills**

JavaScript

ReactJS

Node

HTML, CSS

**SCSS** 

SQL

Visual Basic

Java

Python

C#

## **Interest**

Running	Sci Fi
Surfing	Snowboarding
Sports	Travel

# **Work Experience**

#### **Technology Specialist**

People's Voice On Climate Jan 2021 – Present

- Designed and launched multiple email marketing campaigns with Mailchimp.
- Redesigned UI of company website.
- Configured users permissions and managed finances through Google Workspace Admin.

#### **Implementation Consultant**

Fast Enterprises Sep 2019 – Oct 2020

- Collaborated with a 3rd party vendor to implement a system to process taxpayer data.
- Implemented an electronic filing service that processes tax returns.
- Created data reports, presented demos to clients, and wrote guides and documentation.

## **IT Analyst**

Fantasy Moguls May 2018 – Oct 2018

- Automated the process to retrieve the most up-to-date roster.
- Analyzed the top paying users for asset management.

#### **App Developer**

UM School of Business Sep 2017 – Dec 2017

- Designed, and developed an Android application to collect student data entries.
- Led Scrum meetings with the client to review functional specifications and designs.

# **Related Projects**

#### Softlete

Aug 2021 - Present
A full stack **React** application



Try it View Code

#### Habts

Feb 2021 - Present
A full stack **React** application



**See More** 

# Athletics/Affiliations

## **Sports Performance Trainer**

Freelance

Spring 2021 - Present

#### **Professional Athlete & Coach**

MSA Tigers Football Team (Cairo, Egypt)

Feb 2019 - May 2019

## **Collegiate Athlete**

University of Montana Football Team

Aug 2013 - Dec 2017